Oh no, did I get too close?
我是不是靠的太近？
Oh, did I almost see what's really on the inside?
近的几乎可以透视你内心的真实
All your insecurities
你所有的忐忑不安
All the dirty laundry
你不为人知的秘密
Never made me blink one time
从未一度让我眨眼屏息
Unconditional, unconditionally
我会毫无条件 毫无条件
I will love you unconditionally
我会毫无条件的爱你
There is no fear now
现在卸下恐惧
Let go and just be free
放手一搏 让爱自由
I will love you unconditionally
我会毫无条件的爱你
Come just as you are to me
请你一如既往来我的身边
Don't need apologies
我不需要你的道歉
Know that you are unworthy
我知道你值得我去爱
I'll take your bad days with your good
我要带着你心酸岁月与美丽
Walk through this storm I would
穿越这场肆虐的风雪
I'd do it all because I love you, I love you
我会奋不顾身 因为爱你
Unconditional, unconditionally
我会毫无条件 毫无条件
I will love you unconditionally
我会毫无条件的爱你
There is no fear now
现在卸下恐惧
Let go and just be free
放手一搏 让爱自由
I will love you unconditionally
我会毫无条件的爱你
So open up your heart and just let it begin
敞开你的心扉 让爱迈步前进
Open up your heart, and just let it begin
Open up your heart
敞开你的心扉
Acceptance is the key to be
包容是把钥匙能开启
To be truly free
通往真正自由的门
Will you do the same for me?
你是否也愿意为我不顾一切？
Unconditional, unconditionally
我会毫无条件 毫无条件
I will love you unconditionally
我会毫无条件的爱你
And there is no fear now
现在卸下恐惧
Let go and just be free
放手一搏 让爱自由
'Cause I will love you unconditionally
因为我会毫无条件的爱你
oh ye